Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Who's afraid? Let it break
From shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown
The Psyche awakens, you're never alone
Expect the unexpected.
psyche's show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand the angels are dancing torchlight in
hand let's start the show
hi thank you for coming back um yeah so today early hey what's up guys earlier today i started
I was going to edit out my other thing, but I have to get form bombs for somebody.
So I'm just going to redo it.
But the good thing is, I know the material very well, and I think you should enjoy this
one.
I'll wait until like 10 people get in here.
How are we doing?
I'll show you something new I have, let me see, oh yeah, I can put it like this.
Anyway, I like it.
Let's see, okay, so, let me add this, stay, oh, shit.
You know, I like Trisha Lychis.
Have you ever seen this woman?
She's really cool.
I watched her show tonight, and she was really awesome.
But look at this one, hold on, look at this.
Pretty cool.
Okay, well let's try,
let me insert the, I mean this will be pro-frostarity.
These are some friendship secrets about psychopaths.
Okay, so let me see.
Got the slides.
Copy, yes.
Yes.
I will have my questions up.
I mean you can ask questions on the right side.
This will be a good presentation though.
It will not be dry.
It will be interesting, okay?
Okay, so what do we have?
Today's topic is how to survive a psychopath or surviving psychopathy, not, you know,
having it surviving the toxic individuals that we might encounter that may have that
and they will be...
A parent after a while, it will be very confusing at first if you nerve tell with it
But once you have it will be unmistakable and the more you learn the better you can protect yourself
So I really hope no one's stuck in a relationship with a psychopath that they're not able to exit right now
But we can talk about what psychopathy is and we'll start with that. So what is a psychopath and why does it matter?
And so we have some core traits in the relationship implications of updating a psychopath or being
a friend of one or having one in your family too.
So psychopathy is characterized by a constellation of effective interpersonal and behavioral traits.
Most notably a lack of empathy, okay, so that's going to be one of the key traits, a lack
of empathy.
Manipulativeness and also Machiavellianism that's known as and the impulsivity for impulse control, okay?
Are we?
Let me know if you're here. This is people in the chat. So anyway, so how many people are cycle cut?
It says estimated 1% of the cat has cut a mouse and so she's now estimated 1% of the population the general population is
Considered a psychopath, but it is over-represented in corporate political and intimate relationship contexts
so you're most likely to
work in politics or have a
Relationship with one right they're more most common in those contexts
But victims also describe the relations the dynamic as covertly abusive and emotionally disorienting. Yes
It is a mind fuck. It is confusing. It is a roller coaster and it is abuse, right?
And so we have a subclinical versus a clinical psychopathy.
So subclinical is going to be undiagnosed, right?
And then the clinical is, you know, they're diagnosed.
But many individuals exhibit psychopathic traits
without meeting the full diagnostic criteria.
These subclinical cases often go unnoticed
that are equally capable of sustained emotional abuse
and emotional exploitation.
The reason it's under
You know
The number so small, I think, is because the only diagnosed
psychopathy in prison, I think, they will diagnose and improve.
I guess psychiatrists can, but most of the time, people are diagnosed when they're
in prison. Most people don't go and say, am I a psychopath?
And maybe kids, their parents will think that, and then
we diagnose them then, but most people are diagnosed in a prison.
So a lot of the ones that are outside do not just go and
notice. I think that larger percent of the population, especially in Los Angeles,
We're gonna have larger populations of them.
So why does it matter in relationships?
Because psychopaths lack emotional depth
and reciprocity, making genuine connection impossible.
So you will be trying forever to make this work
and it's unworkable kind of, okay?
The partners may be subject to cycles of idealization
and devaluation, often mistaking early charm
for authentic affection, because they're very good
at wearing masks and so they can be very
early on you know how people you know the first impression so they can make a good impression and
And then we call it switching up right?
then anyway
so you can recognize these manipulative tactics in your relationships and
So let's look at the psychopathic control of intimate dynamics. Okay, so here's some of the the hey, what's up?
Oh the cats are fine and the house is clean. I don't know if they're gonna see the house
Now this is clean, I don't know why people, and it was clean that night too, so I don't know why people are fussing about it, but I'll show you.
It should be called you're about to get banned, but I will show you.
You're just a fucking idiot.
So obviously we have a psychopath in the room and we've acting up already, right?
So this is like that of that person is exhibiting a psychopathic behavior.
So because of that, they will be banished to purgatory by CloudSack.
Anyway, okay, so we have many seven people here, okay, so let's see.
Okay, back to the presentation.
Okay, so what are the tactics they use in relationships, okay, so you can recognize them.
Let me take this one off the screen.
Okay, so in relationships, they'll do love bombing and idealization.
This is the first phase, the idealization phase.
And that is when psychopathic individuals often start relationships with intense flattery,
attention and affection, creating an illusion of perfect compatibility.
The stage is set.
The state is used to disarm the partners' defenses and build dependency, and especially
because some people will be lacking in the feeling of love, they'll feel underappreciated,
and so when they get all this attention all of a sudden, it's like a drug, and it can
be intoxicating, it can feel good, and it's a honeymoon phase.
But the problem is that it's like, you know, it's a mask and the mask will fall
Okay, but it goes gaslighting and cognitive control
So they frequently distort reality deny past statements or actions and project blame to create
confusion and self-doubt in their partner
It'll be a little put down
You know playing with their head. It'll be like, you know, oh, you're crazy or you're, you know, oh calm down
You're always overreacting when they're causing you to react. This is stabilization
Stabilization erodes the victim's confidence and perception. Yeah, because they're like, why can't I like, you know, stand up for myself
They're not understanding why and why why does it like can't they, you know, leave their relationship either. It's hard
And they're like, you know, can't be yourself
self-dehabilitating to your self-confidence, okay?
So there's also exploiting empathy and guilt.
Psychopaths use their partner's compassion against them invoking pity or guilt to excuse
harmful behavior and to avoid accountability.
This emotional leverage keeps victims heathered, okay?
So that's going to be, you know, they're going to have the partner feel sorry for them.
And so, oh, you know, he's a good guy, most of the time he doesn't, you know, he's nice
on, when we're just alone or, I don't know, you're right, it's going to be.
There's going to be a person with a good heart, usually an empath, with the dynamic,
you know, because they can manipulate them easiest.
So then finally we have these microaggressions and covert abuse.
Rather than overt violence, manipulation may manifest your subtle insults, controlling
behavior, or withholding affection, deliberately timed to a road self worth, and without obvious
escalation.
So it's a very passive aggressive way.
It's just unquietly really what's going on, what happened, but I don't know what happened.
You're sitting there just scratching your head.
So the cycle of abuse is then explained, understanding the repetitive nature of psychopathic control.
So there's a few stages, and so there's this tension building phase, and so there's going
to be minor incidents, there's going to be some passive aggressiveness, emotional withdrawal.
And then they'll mark the beginning of the cycle.
Victims often feel like they must walk on eggshells,
anticipating the next outburst, okay?
So there's just tension.
It's like, feels uncomfortable
to walk on eggshells' face, right?
Next gonna happen is there's an incident or an outburst.
So you know, it's like finally boils over
and there's like, you know, they start screaming A.
The phase involves direct psychological,
verbal, or even physical abuse.
The abuser asserts control through intimidation,
humiliation, or manipulation, okay?
What happens after that? There's a reconciliation or the honeymoon period. It says following the abuse, the perpetrator may apologize, offer gifts, or behave affectionately.
This reinforces emotional dependence and fuels hope for change. So, oh, see, that was just, yep, this is emotional abuse and control, you know what, this is what this lecture is about tonight.
Yeah, so this is, the reconciliation is also known as the hoovering phase after they, you know, they'll have an outburst, they'll discard you and then they'll...
Maybe for a while, right when you're about maybe over them, they'll be returning and
then it's like back to the cycle, right?
And then it goes into a state of calm, you know, and it's like the deceptive will occurs
where abuse pauses temporarily, because maybe these things are improving and forcing the
trauma bond and delaying the exit.
The problem is it goes right back to the tension building phase, the tension starts
again, there's another outburst and that's all, the whole thing happens again.
Okay.
So why do people stay in these relationships? Well, there's something called trauma bonding and if you don't know trauma bonding
It's like when you are
doing some emotionally charged situations with somebody and it's like even if they're causing you mostly charged situations you tend that to
Go towards them and grab towards them even stronger. And so
So trauma bonding, it's a psychological response for victims from deep emotional attachments
to their abusers through cycles of abuse and intermittent reinforcement, staking survival
mechanisms for affection, because they're trying to survive, but instead they're thinking
that they're in a loving relationship, but they're...
Basically just trying to survive and so there's also this period of intermittent rewards and reinforcement
So a user's alternate between cruelty and affection, right creating powerful emotional highs and lows
They'll be super nice. They'll be super mean you're like what's going on? Why is it like why are they in two different people, right?
It causes the it mimics the addiction cycle that heightens emotional dependence
There's also the cognitive dissonance. It calls cognitive dissonance is holding two
irreconcilable things
like, you know
in your mind at the same time, like only one of them can be true, but
you believe both of them are the same, so they're a wonderful person,
they're horrible abusers, they're the angel, they're the demon.
Are they both, are they one or the other?
Often, those are just more mass they work, and then we have some barriers to leaving.
Traumabands suppress logical decision-making and increase feelings of guilt, pure obligation.
Pure obligation, guilt, also known as the fog, if you can remember a little acronym,
pure obligation, guilt, these three things will keep us in those relationships.
And in the fog, and in the confusion of the relationship, making it extremely difficult
to tell, to exit the abuse of dynamic, even when the harm is clear.
Yeah, it's usually by the time you do realize it, it's kind of too late sometimes.
and you feel like you're already stuck
and that's where they want you, right?
Okay.
But what's the psychological impact on survivors?
There are mental health consequences
of a psychological abuse,
including the PTSD symptoms, hold on.
Let me just, I'm sorry, I need to go.
I'm sorry.
Psychological impact on survivors, okay.
So they will be, yeah, Jekyll and Hyde,
will be the two personalities.
almost like two different people, right?
So PTSD symptoms, so survivors of these relationships
currently commonly experience flashbacks, nightmares,
hypervigilance, and emotional numbing.
These symptoms mirror post-traumatic stress disorder
due to prolonged emotional trauma.
There's also shame, guilt, and self-blame,
where victims often internalize the abuser's narrative,
believing they're responsible for the abuse.
The emotional confusion undermines self-worth
and delays the recovery.
Right because when you're ashamed guilty or blaming yourself you cannot feel good about yourself, right?
Because you're in these negative emotional states
You're also emotionally de-disregulated. So you're gonna have mood swings anxiety depression
difficulty managing stress and maybe even trusting in future relationships
So this is not only like ruin that relationship
We can ruin like love for you all together. You're like, you know, trust people anymore
Maybe friends or even lovers or family. You won't trust anybody sometimes
But you also lose your identity in isolation, slowly taking on the psychopaths, they will
slowly erode your identity, replacing with yours, you'll also learn how to project your
good qualities onto them, and so you're actually, because they're so empty, and so they can
be the perfect projection of whatever you put onto them, and so you can see them as
perfect, and they, you know.
That's not that so but actually you're falling in love with yourself sometimes, right?
Isn't that ironic and you're just projecting all of your own your own good qualities onto them falling in love with yourself
Right, but survivors may feel fragmented socially isolated and struggle with decision-making or a certain boundaries. Okay
We have questions in the chat. Let me know if you have a question go ahead and shout out say hi
Let me know if you've also been in these really kind of relationships
Where you are? I mean if you are in this relationship or how where you are in the relationship if you're on no contact if you're
If you're familiar with this or you're just interested in knowing this just for if it happens in the future or
You know, you know, hopefully you're not in the midst of something very very bad because these can be very very damaging to our lives
Okay, so next slide, let's go, okay, so then we have a coping method for it, okay, so this
is the way to, this is for the short term, okay, this is going to be maybe for friendships,
this will work the best, or your employment, a competitor, in relationships this probably
Just hound you if you do this, okay? So this is the gray rock method, okay?
It means detachment strategy against the psychopathic manipulation
So basically what you do is there's the gray rock method involves it becoming emotionally unresponsive
Disengaged interactions with them and if you live individual
Reducing their incentive to provoke or exploit now now on the internet. We have a lot of trolls, right?
And so I think you can almost replace psychopathic
troll or you know a troll with narcissists. I mean like not all right it's like some
are you know there's friendly trolls and there's you know non harmful ones but a
lot of these especially these ones that bring you little activity are gonna be
psychopathic and unfortunate they're running a lot of you know things now
they're doing some very bad things you know extortion etc.
But why does it work?
So it's because psychopaths are looking for the emotional reactions and control.
Grey Rocking removes the emotional fuel that's rivaled off of making the target less appealing
or engaged.
It's kind of like, you know, you want to look like a rock to them on Grey Rocking.
It might be as interesting as a rock.
So they're not going to be like...
I'm going to go to this person, I'm going to get this high from the set, which is what
trolls want too, they want the emotional fuel, it's like a cold fuel, right?
But anyway, if you want to implement this, keep the communication minimal, factual, neutral,
no sharing opinions, don't share emotions, don't share personal stories or updates, maintain
consistent boundaries, and keep your emotions very, very steady, don't, don't, don't, don't
Don't have them up or down right, but there's a warning. It's like a it's useful in the short term this strategy
But it will not a long it's not a long-term solution and may escalate risk in some of the closer relationships like every
Romantic relationship may escalate
Okay, but next we need to think about escape from these situations. Okay, so we have the safety planning and escape, right?
So you have to recognize there's an imminent risk and your life is in danger
So you have to trust your instincts. You'll feel something like you'll feel like okay. This is the time to go
This is if I don't something bad's gonna happen. The threats have been escalating, right?
They have the control your finances that they told your friends or physical
There's physical violence or they're like, you know
Isolating you from your family, right or friends. So you prioritize your personal safety over make up the emotional resolution of the relationship
That's what you think about first, is your safety, right?
Feeling unsafe, you gotta get out of this situation.
So you prepare an exit strategy,
which may involve creating an escape plan.
You pack your essentials, your IDs, you get a burner phone,
you get friends that are not gonna tell you where you are,
you know, your social media.
You know, you get all your medications
and your money ready, right?
Identify safe contacts and shelters,
secure transportation and advance
and avoid any digital traces, okay?
It's going to be a scary time if you have to do this, but unfortunately they will probably
be looking for you and trying to hoover you back, and they're not going to like you.
So you also want to be documenting all this abuse with, you know, keep evidence, screenshots,
photos, journal entries, witness testimonies, can support legal action.
If you ever need a restraining order, you can pull out this book and say, here is all the
history of what they've done.
You also involve professionals. You want to make sure you talk to a
License or you know
Psychologist therapist and life coach even a psychic
You know that somebody that you
Do you trust to keep your secrets and also somebody that can give you good advice and listen to you at least now
That's the most important thing listen to you
But after you give it to escape you're gonna need to do something else
Which is learning how to set these boundaries and finding you can support systems, okay?
So, this is how you regain the control after the abuse.
You establish clear boundaries in your relationships, that's how you receive your personal autonomy
freedom by defining emotional, physical and digital boundaries.
Be consistent and a sort of manipulator exploits ambiguity and hesitation.
So, you can't have any ambiguity, you can't have any gray areas with it because they will
exploit those areas.
fighting about it, there's no argument. It's just like, no, it's my boundary.
I'm not going to be talking to you or be involved with you because you're going over my boundaries.
Let them know your clear boundaries. You also want to rebuild your support networks,
which have probably been eroded, and by the narcissist
who tries to isolate you, which is one of their key
tactics to get away from your support systems.
They also want to utilize the professional help, talk to the therapists, support groups,
domestic violence advocates, trauma-informed professionals can help you develop tools to
increase your resilience, okay, they're specialist at it.
Also practicing self-care as resistant.
Recovery requires nourishment, physical, emotional, and spiritual.
Sleep nutrition, mindfulness, and creativity are not luxuries, they're survival strategies,
okay.
You're going to want to be doing these things, make sure you're eating right, make sure you're sleeping enough, and you're on your right mind, especially if you're going to be tempted.
But here's the most effective strategy, and this is what everyone will tell you, this is the answer. This is the answer, it's not the answer like a lot of people want to hear, they would like to continue the relationship and be friends and things like that.
It doesn't really work, it doesn't always work, they'll always be trying to pull you back in, they're never going to change, they're never going to...
They're always going to try and elate, and others think that it's going to be hell.
But you know some people can adapt to that, but I wouldn't recommend it.
But no contact means cutting ties to regain your power and peace,
which you will forfeit if you stay with them, right?
So what no contact means?
The no contact rule involves eliminating all forms of communication.
So that means you change your phone number, calls, email, social media.
You block them everywhere.
No avenue to connect to it.
maybe they'll have to like know where you live and then it's like that you can get the police
if they come to your door and you tell them not to come over, right? Why it's critical,
continued communication prolongs the trauma bonding, it gives the user opportunities to
manipulate, a guilt trip, regain control, no contact, sepers is completely, right?
It's the only way to really do it.
So you just want to block numbers, change email, update privacy settings, the way checking
their online activity, digital boundaries are vital, as well as the physical ones.
But breaking contact can feel unbearable at first due to emotional cravings caused by
trauma.
Because this will be like a drug, almost some of these feelings that you get with them will
These chemicals they know how to release these chemicals the dopamine in your brain will release around them sometimes
They'll get addicted to actual people right like a drug
so contact can feel unbearable and
Yeah, so support systems and accountability partners can prevent relapse. We got an account to build a buddy, right?
It's like you can call them if you're feeling cravings to see the person and then they can say hey
Remember the person that dismissed you said you're not going to talk to them remember the hell you went through
Need somebody like that
Excuse me next
We have
Seeking professional and peer support you can heal through therapy and community
So there's some some different kinds of therapy that you might want to look into if you are trying to recover
There's trauma-informed therapy. Specialized therapists can help survivors first process complex PTSD
rebuild self-esteem and address emotional dysregulation caused by prolonged abuse.
That's going to be some kind of like like active therapy where it's like, you know
You're gonna be probably exposed exposure therapy to like some of this and then work through these triggers
Support groups and peer networks, you know, might want to have a support group and also have friends that have been through the same thing.
You can share experiences, you can learn from each other, and you can also be a social outlet for each other that's safe from the abusers.
Also,
There's hotlines, advocacy systems, there's the domestic violence, the crisis hotlines,
domestic violence, organizations, CYCID hotlines, anything that pertains to what you're feeling
at the time.
There's also holistic healing, you might want to go get a massage, you might want to go
get a journaling, art therapy, body-based practices, and these things can also aid recovery
and bring you back into your body, okay?
Because you're probably in the ether a lot of the time during this really it will put you in an emotional ether
Or it's very easy to manipulate because you're going all by your emotions. Okay, so we have healing and reclaiming your identity
So beyond the psychopathic abuse
What you're going to want to do is a few things you're going to want to rebuild yourself worth that has been eroded
Survivors often emerge fractured self-esteem healing involves affirming intrinsic value celebrating small victories
rejecting internalized blame
They want to reclaim their autonomy, which is like the freedom to do what they want when
they want to make their own decisions, making independent decisions about lifestyle, relationships,
or career, restores personal power when it's undermined by manipulation and control, because
you're not able to make these decisions on your own when you're with these people, right?
Also, we have to relearn trust trust is not just about others
But also one self because maybe we don't trust yourself after you like keep going to these relationships, right?
And it's like we need to like learn how to trust ourselves and know that we're not going to
Put ourselves in these bad situations, but sometimes it's a hard lesson, right?
We also want to live authentically embrace our passions creativity and personal growth and
That will provide a sense of identity and meaning beyond that the abusers shadow that may look along after the relationship
Okay, next we have
Empowerment and resilience. So we can move forward beyond psychopathic abuse.
Okay, so here's what we can do. Transform survival into strength, right?
When you survive, you're not just a survivor, though. You're strong.
To survive, you need to be strong, right? So survivors embody the resilience by
turning powerful, painful experiences into sources of wisdom and empowerment,
inspiring themselves and others. Imagine being able to help people now that you've
been through it, right?
So you can advocate for yourself and others you can speak out share your story engage in advocacy and that transforms your isolation
Into solidarity with others creates awareness that protects future victims, right?
That's all it can do is be good, right?
You also want to cultivate future relationships with people that respect your boundaries
You have trust and empathy with and better help your more authentic connections because the you know
You'll just be in a false time-wasting relationship with these psychopaths
Finally, you want to embrace a renewed identity, so it's not just about bouncing back, it's
about growing stronger, rediscovering your purpose, and driving beyond the sense of
you've been abused.
Okay.
So, I'm going to go through this abuse cycle in detail again.
It goes through these phases.
I don't know if we went through them before, but I'm going to tell you the other ones.
They're also known as the tension building.
So, there's the stress mounting through criticism.
This is also called the devaluation phase, it's this tension building.
So, there's going to be the withdrawal, criticism, silent hostility, devaluing, taking up the
pedestal.
Phase two is there's going to be this secret abuse, it's called acute abuse, and so it's
It's verbal attacks, psychological manipulation, physical violence, the most overtly harmful
phase, right?
Then we have the reconciliation phase, and then finally, things go back to normal, but
the reconciliation phase is called the Hoover stage, and when things go back to normal,
the calm, calm before the storm, because it's right before those love bombs about to go
off, right?
Okay.
So we can also visualize the abuse cycle. It looks like this. It looks like this.
It circles within circles within circles. The circular pattern of control and manipulation.
So stress accumulates through criticism, withdrawal, and subtle aggression.
The abuser asserts control through intimidation, manipulation, or violence.
So it's just a nightmare. It's like a nightmare of a cycle, correct? Okay?
So there's some long-term recovery practices. Of course, you know rebuilding the healthy relationships
Moving on the post-traumatic stress you grow post trauma. You also learn mindfulness and compassion
new meditations a good thing to pick up
Self reflection like going inside yourself falling in love with yourself too and also being consistent in your care
Regular therapy, journaling, exercise, community involvement,
create the structure for yourself for a long-term recovery that can be successful.
Okay, we have 25% more of the presentation left.
So now we are in the post-traumatic growth stage.
Transforming the trauma into your empowerment, you redefine strength.
You discover inner strength, resilience, determination, and courage that you didn't know you had before.
So you have these superpowers, right?
You also become clear on your values, now you know what you don't want and you do want,
now you know what you cherish and you don't cherish, so you get some benefits from leaving
these relationships.
Your empathy and your connections will improve and increase, you'll heighten empathy, be
able to use your pain to give your compassion to other people, and you can renew your purpose,
new life paths that give their experiences a greater meaning, okay.
So we can look for some more common traits and the red flags. These are the biggest ones, right?
It says, uh, so they have the superficial charm and intensity. So psychopaths often present as
charismatic, attentive, and overly flattering early in relationships, creating a sense of instinct
They have a lack of empathy or remorse.
They show little genuine concern for others' feelings, dismissed pain they've caused or
rationalized their abuse and often blaming the victim.
They have the gaslighting and manipulation, denial of past actions, assortment of reality.
And then they have this pattern of exploitation where they just tend to follow the idealization,
devaluation, discard, leaving victims strained and disoriented, okay.
So here's some potential red flags to watch out for if you are concerned that you might be in a relationship with a psychopath
There's too much too soon. So excessive flattery rushing intimacy or demands for commitment early on
These are common manipulation tactics. Just to get you you know sign on the dotted line right now. It's like great
You don't have time to think, right?
Inconsistencies in the stories, frequent contradictions,
lies or evasions about past relationships,
or behavior indicate dishonesty, okay?
There's also control or isolation
when they discourage contact with your friends and family,
monitor your activities, restrict your autonomy.
Are those a major red flag that you might be in a relationship
with an abuser or a psychopath?
Finally, emotional roller coaster,
extreme shifts between affection and cruelty,
leaving you confused, anxious, or doubting your memory,
suggests deliberate manipulation.
Trademarks finally we have a
We have some resources, so we have the national domestic violence hotline number. We have the crisis text line
We have some books
Recommended Psychopath free by Jackson McKenzie women who love psychopaths by Sandra Brown the body keeps the score by Bursel Bender cook
We have some support in organizations like domesticshelters.org, RAIN, which is the R-A-P-E
Abuse, I-N-T-E-S-T National Network, local women's shelters providing practical support.
There's also online communities, probably the easiest ones to hook up with, you know,
and maybe the safest.
And that is our presentation.
And so I hope that was interesting.
I hope that was enlightening.
conversation, important topics. I'm going to be doing these special classes maybe
once or twice a week. They will be great. I'd really appreciate if you could help
support the show and me doing these presentations by offering a donation.
or buying a membership or just sharing it live, you know?
I appreciate all those things.
So if you have any questions, I know it's been very quiet.
I'm not sure exactly why it's been so quiet,
but I am gonna wrap up the show tonight.
I will maybe be back to that, I'm not sure,
but I just wanted to get this all out on tape
and have the official.
Have the official school school with psyche start. Okay, so I hope you enjoyed your first class and
Will be a test
I'll be back guys. I'm I'll be back probably tonight or this morning, but I'm doing a nice
Nice night. Thank you for watching